jaguarlandrover.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Jaguar Land Rover Corporate Website

Jaguar Land Rover Limited ("We", “Us”, “Jaguar Land Rover”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy (together with our [Terms of Use](http://www.jaguarlandrover.com/gl/en/about-us/terms-of-website-use/ "Terms of Website Use") and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us through the [www.jaguarlandrover.com](http://www.jaguarlandrover.com/) website (the “Site”), will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting the Site you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Jaguar Land Rover Limited (“We”, “Us” or “Jaguar Land Rover”) of Abbey Road, Whitley, Coventry, CV3 4LF (registered as a data controller with the ICO with registration number ZA 020510).

Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information you give us. You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our Site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you subscribe to one of our services, search for a product, and when you report a problem with our Site. The information you give us may include (but is not limited to) your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal description and photograph and details of your enquiry.
  * Information we collect about you. We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself however with regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information:
  * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
  * Information we receive from other sources. We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

How do we use your information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * Information you give to us. We will use this information:
  * to respond to any enquiries or requests for information you may have sent to us;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you may request from us;
  * to notify you about changes to our service; and
  * to ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * Information we collect about you. We will use this information:
  * to administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * to improve our Site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure;
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
  * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
  * Information we receive from other sources. We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you through other sources e.g. Google Analytics. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

Disclosure of your information

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries (as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006).

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Site.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Jaguar Land Rover or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](http://www.jaguarlandrover.com/gl/en/about-us/terms-of-website-use/ "Terms of Website Use") and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Jaguar Land Rover, our customers, or others. This includes, where relevant, exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Where we store your personal data

Jaguar Land Rover operates in many countries. To offer a consistent service to you we manage our Sites from one central site that is currently located in the United Kingdom. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored here. It may also be processed by staff operating in other countries who work for us or for one of our suppliers.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable privacy laws

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by [contacting us](http://www.jaguarlandrover.com/gl/en/contact/ "Contact").

Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

Access to information

You have the right to access information that we hold about you. Any access request may be subject to a small fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve its performance. For detailed information on the cookies we use, the purposes for which we use them and to learn about how to manage cookies, please see below.

By continuing to browse the Site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

Information about our use of cookies

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

We use the following cookies:

Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them below:

Name: __utma, __utmb, __utmz

Cookie Type: Persistent third party cookie

Prupose: These cookies enable the function of Google Analytics. This software helps us take and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, response to marketing activity and browsing times. That information helps us to improve the website and your experience, and to make our marketing campaigns relevant.  
These cookies can be turned off via your web browser, and will not affect the user’s experience.

Name: JLR_allowCookie

Cookie Type: Persistent first party cookie

Prupose: This cookie remembers your acceptance of the use of cookies on the website and hides the notification banner.

This cookie can be turned off via your web browser, and will result in the use of cookie notification banner displaying.

Managing Cookies  
Disabling and Enabling Cookies

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled. Guideline instructions on how to check cookies are enabled follow below:

How to check cookies are enabled for PC’s

Google Chrome  
1\. Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select Options   
2\. Click the 'Under the Hood' tab, locate the 'Privacy' section, and select the 'Content settings' button   
3\. Now select 'Allow local data to be set'

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.0, 7.0, 8.0  
1\. Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Internet options' , then click on the 'Privacy' tab   
2\. Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below, which will enable cookies in your browser   
3\. Settings above Medium will disable cookies

Mozilla Firefox  
1\. Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select Options   
2\. Then select the Privacy icon   
3\. Click on Cookies, then select 'allow sites to set cookies'

Safari  
1\. Click on the Cog icon at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option   
2\. Click on 'Security', check the option that says 'Block third-party and advertising cookies'   
3\. Click 'Save'

How to check cookies are enabled for Macs

Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.0 on OSX  
1\. Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Internet options' , then click on the 'Privacy' tab   
2\. Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below, which will enable cookies in your browser   
3\. Settings above Medium will disable cookies

Safari on OSX  
1\. Click on 'Safari' at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option   
2\. Click on 'Security' then 'Accept cookies'   
3\. Select the 'Only from site you navigate to'

Mozilla and Netscape on OSX  
1\. Click on 'Mozilla' or 'Netscape' at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option   
2\. Scroll down until you see cookies under 'Privacy & Security'   
3\. Select 'Enable cookies for the originating web site only'

Opera  
1\. Click on 'Menu' at the top of your browser window and select 'Settings'   
2\. Then select 'Preferences', select the 'Advanced' tab   
3\. Then select 'Accept cookies' option

Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our Site.

Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to Jaguar Land Rover, Abbey Road, Whitley, Coventry, CV3 4LH.
